[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This extremely large and tall German dog breed has a very short shiny coat and strong muscular body with a majestic posture.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["German Mastiff", "Boarhound", "Great Dane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I shot a man at close range through his head with a bow and arrow. Who am I?", "correct_answer": "Rambo", "incorrect_answers": ["John Mcclane", "The Terminator", "Indiana Jones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A pharmacist was compounding a mixture for a topical antibiotic. Using the apothecary system, how many pounds did he make if the end product resulted in having twenty-four 3.5 ounce tubes?", "correct_answer": "7 pounds", "incorrect_answers": ["6.5 pounds", "5.25 pounds", "6 pounds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these movies tells the story of Littlefoot, an Apatosaurus in search of the Great Valley where dinosaurs can live in peace?", "correct_answer": "The Land Before Time", "incorrect_answers": ["Walking With Dinosaurs", "Jurassic Park", "King Kong"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first European nation to grant women the right to vote?", "correct_answer": "Finland", "incorrect_answers": ["Norway", "Austria", "Ireland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This lawyers unspoken last thought is, It is a far, far better thing that I do, than I have ever done; it is a far, far better rest that I go to, than I have ever known.", "correct_answer": "Sydney Carton", "incorrect_answers": ["Bradley J. Stevens", "Allen Sneed", "Joel McCreadle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sharks rarely attack humans.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What board game does Rick play throughout the 1942 film, Casablanca?", "correct_answer": "Chess", "incorrect_answers": ["Mancala", "Risk", "Go"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1927 movie The Jazz Singer, ranked #90 on the AFI list, is famous primarily for what?", "correct_answer": "It was the first talkie.", "incorrect_answers": ["It co-starred Charlie Chaplin as himself.", "None of these", "It was the first color film."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Mel Brooks films, released in the period 1968-1995, were recast into Broadway musicals?", "correct_answer": "2", "incorrect_answers": ["1", "4", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Red is believed to provoke hunger.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What historical figure does Charlie Chaplin satirize in his 1940 comedy movie The Great Dictator?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Benito Mussolini", "Adolf Hitler", "Napoleon Bonaparte"]}]